Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Light Beyond the Reed=
=النور وراء القصب=
(Adapted from the Jinjiang novel "Light Beyond the Reed" by Mo Shubai)
(مقتبس من رواية جينجيانج "الضوء وراء القصب" لمو شوباي)
=Episode 4=
=الحلقة 4=
Why did you come back?
لماذا عدت؟
Do you...
هل أنت...
Do you want something to eat?
هل تريد شيئا لتأكله؟
Have a seat first.
خذ مقعدًا أولاً.
When did you start drinking?
متى بدأت بالشرب؟
Just...
فقط...
Just recently.
مؤخرا.
Did you buy the cigarettes too?
هل اشتريت السجائر أيضاً؟
Sibei.
سيب.
What's going on with you?
ماذا يحدث معك؟
I...
أنا...
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Work has just been stressful lately.
لقد كان العمل مرهقًا في الآونة الأخيرة.
I needed to let off some steam.
كنت بحاجة إلى التخلص من بعض البخار.
It's not a big deal.
إنها ليست مشكلة كبيرة.
I just had a few drinks.
لقد تناولت للتو بضعة مشروبات.
I'm an adult now.
أنا شخص بالغ الآن.
That's not illegal, right?
هذا ليس غير قانوني، أليس كذلك؟
Do you have anything to tell me?
هل لديك شيئا لتخبرني به؟
You came for the divorce papers, didn't you?
لقد أتيت من أجل أوراق الطلاق، أليس كذلك؟
Or do you want to finalize it today?
أم تريد الانتهاء منه اليوم؟
I'll get them for you.
سأحضرها لك.
Why did you suddenly agree to the divorce?
لماذا وافقت فجأة على الطلاق؟
Can you give me a reason?
هل يمكنك أن تعطيني سبب؟
There's no reason.
لا يوجد سبب.
You want a divorce, so be it.
تريد الطلاق فليكن.
What happened
ماذا حدث
on the night of April 9th?
في ليلة 9 أبريل؟
I'll get you a pen.
سأحضر لك قلمًا.
On the night of April 9th,
في ليلة التاسع من أبريل،
your company had a drinking engagement.
كانت شركتك لديها التزام بالشرب.
You got drunk.
لقد سكرت.
You and Chuchu got into Fan Jiancheng's car.
صعدت أنت وتشوتشو إلى سيارة Fan Jiancheng.
After Chuchu was dropped off,
بعد أن تم إنزال تشوتشو،
you were taken to the canola field.
لقد تم نقلك إلى حقل الكانولا.
When you woke up,
عندما استيقظت،
you called the police.
لقد اتصلت بالشرطة.
But why you withdrew the report
ولكن لماذا سحبت التقرير؟
when they arrived?
عندما وصلوا؟
Ye Sibei.
أيها سيبي.
Who was it?
من كان؟
Since you already know everything,
بما أنك تعرف كل شيء بالفعل،
what's left to say?
ماذا بقي لي أن أقول؟
Does it matter who it was?
هل يهم من كان؟
I'm not reporting it.
أنا لا أبلغ عن ذلك.
Was it Fan Jiancheng?
هل كان فان جيانتشنغ؟
I don't remember.
أنا لا أتذكر.
One of the bosses
أحد الرؤساء
at the drinking engagement loves drinking.
في حفل الشرب يحب الشرب.
He insisted I drink too.
وأصر على أن أشرب أيضًا.
I didn't want to trouble everyone,
لم أكن أريد أن أزعج الجميع،
so I drank what they poured.
فشربت ما سكبوه.
Later, my mom called me
لاحقا اتصلت بي أمي
about our divorce.
حول طلاقنا.
We argued.
لقد تجادلنا.
And somehow,
وبطريقة ما،
I drank a few more glasses.
شربت بضعة أكواب أخرى.
After that,
بعد ذلك،
Fan Jiancheng offered to drive me home.
عرض علي فان جيانتشنغ أن يقودني إلى المنزل.
He said I asked to get off
قال أنني طلبت النزول
when we were almost home.
عندما كنا على وشك الوصول إلى المنزل.
But I don't remember anything.
ولكنني لا أتذكر أي شيء.
When I woke up the next day,
عندما استيقظت في اليوم التالي،
I was in a canola field.
كنت في حقل الكانولا.
I called the police
لقد اتصلت بالشرطة
and asked them to bring me a coat.
وطلبت منهم أن يحضروا لي معطفًا.
The police are willing to help you.
الشرطة على استعداد لمساعدتك.
So am I.
وكذلك أنا.
Why carry this burden alone?
لماذا تحمل هذا العبء وحدك؟
I've figured it out.
لقد توصلت إلى ذلك.
What good would reporting it do?
ما الفائدة من الإبلاغ عنه؟
People would just say it was my fault anyway.
على أي حال ، الناس سوف يقولون أن هذا كان خطئي.
It's like when kids fight.
إنه مثل عندما يتشاجر الأطفال.
You get hit on the left cheek.
لقد تعرضت لضربة على الخد الأيسر.
Why go home just to get hit
لماذا العودة إلى المنزل فقط من أجل التعرض للضرب؟
on the right too?
على اليمين أيضا؟
It takes two to tango.
يتطلب الأمر اثنين للتانجو.
I wasn't careful enough.
لم أكن حذرا بما فيه الكفاية.
It's not a big deal.
إنها ليست مشكلة كبيرة.
I'll just forget it.
سوف أنسى ذلك.
I just
انا فقط
did you wrong.
هل أخطأت؟
What did you do wrong?
ماذا فعلت خطأ؟
You just did your job.
لقد قمت بعملك للتو.
Going home after work. What did you do wrong?
العودة إلى المنزل بعد العمل. ما الخطأ الذي ارتكبته؟
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Let's go to the police.
دعنا نذهب إلى الشرطة.
No.
لا.
No!
لا!
It's over.
انتهى.
I didn't report it then. Why now?
لم أبلغ عن ذلك حينها. لماذا الآن؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I don't need to make a police report. I don't need!
لا أحتاج إلى تقديم بلاغ للشرطة. لا أحتاج!
If you don't report to the police, will you really be fine?
إذا لم تبلغ الشرطة، هل ستكون بخير حقًا؟
I'll do fine.
سأفعل جيدا.
I don't need to call the police.
لا أحتاج إلى الاتصال بالشرطة.
If you want a divorce, then do it.
إذا كنت تريد الطلاق فافعل ذلك.
I only ask one thing. Just let it go, okay?
أطلب شيئًا واحدًا فقط. دع الأمر يمر، حسنًا؟
As long as we stay silent,
طالما بقينا صامتين،
this will be over.
هذا سوف ينتهي.
I'll pack up.
سأحزم أمتعتي.
I'll pack up right now.
سأجمع أمتعتي الآن.
Ye Sibei.
أيها سيبي.
If the harm isn't fairly addressed,
إذا لم يتم التعامل مع الضرر بشكل عادل،
the wound will stay rotten forever.
الجرح سوف يبقى فاسدا إلى الأبد.
This is only the beginning.
هذه مجرد البداية .
You'll slowly rot from inside out.
سوف تتعفن ببطء من الداخل إلى الخارج.
You'll spend half your life
سوف تقضي نصف حياتك
trying to heal that wound.
محاولة شفاء هذا الجرح.
You'll keep wondering
ستظل تتساءل
why it happened to you
لماذا حدث لك ذلك
and what you did wrong.
وما الخطأ الذي فعلته.
Why the one who hurt you
لماذا الشخص الذي يؤذيك
can live well,
يمكن أن يعيش جيدا،
while you end up like this?
بينما انتهيت مثل هذا؟
Everything you do now...
كل ما تفعله الآن...
Everyone will pity you
الجميع سوف يشفق عليك
because you're a victim.
لأنك ضحية.
But in the future
ولكن في المستقبل
when people forget your pain
عندما ينسى الناس ألمك
and only see what your life became,
ولا ترى إلا ما أصبحت عليه حياتك،
they'll just think
سوف يفكرون فقط
Ye Sibei is worthless.
يي سيبي لا قيمة له.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
I'm worthless.
أنا لا قيمة لي.
My mom said
قالت أمي
we must accept fate.
علينا أن نقبل القدر.
Fate can be changed!
يمكن تغيير القدر!
Sibei.
سيب.
You must try to win once.
يجب عليك أن تحاول الفوز مرة واحدة.
Just once.
مرة واحدة فقط.
But I've never won!
ولكنني لم أفوز أبدًا!
You think I haven't tried?
هل تعتقد أنني لم أحاول؟
I tried.
لقد حاولت.
When I was little,
عندما كنت صغيرا،
I thought studying hard could change my life.
اعتقدت أن الدراسة الجادة قد تغير حياتي.
But it didn't.
ولكن لم يحدث ذلك.
I thought working hard
اعتقدت أن العمل الجاد
could change my life.
قد يغير حياتي.
But it didn't.
ولكن لم يحدث ذلك.
I thought the hardest time was always now
اعتقدت أن أصعب وقت كان دائمًا الآن
and that better days would come once I got through it.
وأن أيامًا أفضل ستأتي بعد أن أتجاوزها.
But in the end,
ولكن في النهاية،
there's always more pain ahead.
هناك دائما المزيد من الألم في المستقبل.
There are always harder things
هناك دائما أشياء أصعب
waiting in the future.
الانتظار في المستقبل.
I'm not disciplined enough.
أنا لست منضبطًا بما فيه الكفاية.
Not smart enough.
ليس ذكيا بما فيه الكفاية.
Not careful enough.
ليس حذرا بما فيه الكفاية.
I'm foolish, sentimental,
أنا أحمق، عاطفي،
low in emotional IQ, and married with no kids.
منخفض الذكاء العاطفي، ومتزوج وليس لديه أطفال.
No company wants me.
لا تريدني أي شركة.
How can I be picky?
كيف يمكنني أن أكون انتقائيا؟
I have a degree
لدي شهادة جامعية
but still earn 3,500 yuan a month.
لكن لا يزال يكسب 3500 يوان شهريا.
Haven't I been blamed enough?
ألم يتم إلقاء اللوم علي بما فيه الكفاية؟
You tell me to win,
أنت تطلب مني الفوز،
but how can I win?
ولكن كيف يمكنني الفوز؟
I only want one thing now.
أريد شيئا واحدا فقط الآن.
I want to live well.
أريد أن أعيش جيدا.
I want to live like an ordinary person.
أريد أن أعيش كأي شخص عادي.
No fighting, no rebellion,
لا قتال، لا تمرد،
just go with the flow,
فقط اذهب مع التدفق،
and live without any expectation.
والعيش دون أي توقعات.
Is that too much to ask?
هل هذا كثير جدًا؟
You say you want to give up,
تقول أنك تريد الاستسلام،
but inside lives another you,
لكن في الداخل تعيش أنت آخر،
who never gave up.
الذين لم يستسلموا أبدًا.
Sibei.
سيب.
If you want to live
إذا كنت تريد أن تعيش
like a normal person,
مثل أي شخص عادي،
then report to the police with me.
ثم أبلغ الشرطة معي.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Chuchu said
قال تشوتشو
Nan beat up Fan Jiancheng.
قام نان بضرب فان جيانتشنغ.
So I came to see.
لذلك جئت لرؤية.
I heard you arguing, so I didn't knock.
لقد سمعتك تتجادل، لذلك لم أطرق الباب.
Maybe I should come inside first.
ربما يجب علي أن أدخل أولاً.
Nianwen.
نيانوين.
Move aside.
تنحى جانبا.
Calling the police now
اتصل بالشرطة الآن
will have a low chance of winning.
ستكون فرص الفوز منخفضة.
Is that what you should tell your sister?
هل هذا ما يجب أن تقوله لأختك؟
Is that what a lawyer should say?
هل هذا ما يجب أن يقوله المحامي؟
I can't let her fight a losing case!
لا أستطيع أن أسمح لها بمحاربة قضية خاسرة!
You're not her.
أنت لست هي.
You're not her family.
أنت لست عائلتها.
You don't know her pain.
أنت لا تعرف ألمها.
Everyone will doubt her from the start.
الجميع سوف يشك فيها منذ البداية.
Why did she drink that night?
لماذا شربت تلك الليلة؟
What was her relation to the defendant?
ما هي علاقتها بالمتهم؟
They'll examine her past, her family,
سوف يقومون بفحص ماضيها وعائلتها،
every act they call improper.
كل فعل يسمونه غير لائق.
They'll say she seduced him and framed him.
سيقولون أنها أغوته ووقعت به في الفخ.
If she loses the case,
إذا خسرت القضية،
they'll say she set him up in a honey trap.
سيقولون أنها وضعته في فخ العسل.
They'll say she asked for money and failed.
سيقولون أنها طلبت المال وفشلت.
She was trying to be a homewrecker. Even accusing her of indecent work.
كانت تحاول أن تكون مُخربة منازل، حتى أنها اتهمتها بعملٍ غير لائق.
I understand your anger.
أنا أفهم غضبك.
If you can't accept it,
إذا لم تتمكن من قبول ذلك،
you can get a divorce.
يمكنك الحصول على الطلاق.
But I can't watch you ruin my sister.
ولكنني لا أستطيع أن أشاهدك تدمر أختي.
You saw me at the hospital that day, right?
لقد رأيتني في المستشفى ذلك اليوم، أليس كذلك؟
You said those things on purpose,
لقد قلت هذه الأشياء عن قصد،
just to make me give up reporting it?
فقط لتجعلني أتوقف عن الإبلاغ عنه؟
Don't follow me.
لا تتبعني.
(Gynecology Clinic)
(عيادة أمراض النساء)
Don't force it.
لا تجبرها.
What kind of parent is this?
ما نوع هذا الوالد؟
Let him go.
دعوه يذهب.
Look.
ينظر.
You've already fought twice at the beginning.
لقد قاتلت مرتين في البداية.
If you can't even handle this,
إذا لم تتمكن حتى من التعامل مع هذا،
what will you do after we report it?
ماذا ستفعل بعد أن نبلغ عنه؟
Violence solves nothing.
العنف لا يحل شيئا
Everyone's very clear-headed.
الجميع لديهم ذهن صافٍ للغاية.
My mom.
أمي.
My brother.
أخي.
Everyone's very clear-headed.
الجميع لديهم ذهن صافٍ للغاية.
All of you should go.
ينبغي عليكم جميعا أن تذهبوا.
I want to be alone for a while.
أريد أن أكون وحدي لفترة من الوقت.
Sibei.
سيب.
♪A ray of light and a spark in the dark night♪
شعاع من الضوء وشرارة في ليلة مظلمة؟؟؟
♪Is it enough to dream?♪
???هل يكفي أن نحلم ؟؟؟؟
♪Bubbles floating♪
???فقاعات عائمة؟؟؟
♪Light refracting♪
???انكسار الضوء؟؟؟
♪Neon♪
؟؟؟نيون؟؟؟
♪Chase that beam of neon♪
???مطاردة شعاع النيون هذا؟؟؟
♪Let it cover all of me♪
???دعه يغطيني بالكامل؟؟؟
♪Can't hear who's crying♪
???لا أستطيع سماع من يبكي؟؟؟
♪Keep on laughing♪
???استمر في الضحك؟؟؟
♪Who still cares♪
???ومن لا يزال يهتم؟؟؟
♪About the neon you can't escape?♪
???حول النيون الذي لا يمكنك الهروب منه ؟؟؟؟
♪The colorful trap is too dazzling♪
???الفخ الملون مبهر للغاية؟؟؟
♪Jump into this void♪
???القفز في هذا الفراغ؟؟؟
♪Never to see again♪
???لن نرى مرة أخرى؟؟؟
♪That dream that ended suddenly♪
???ذلك الحلم الذي انتهى فجأة؟؟؟
Nan.
في.
You knew all along.
لقد عرفت ذلك طوال الوقت.
Even your mom knew.
حتى والدتك عرفت.
You're indeed a family.
أنتم عائلة بالفعل.
Nan, listen to me.
نان، استمعي لي.
My sister didn't call the police
لم تتصل أختي بالشرطة
because my mom and I stopped her.
لأن أمي وأنا أوقفناها.
All the blame is on us.
اللوم كله علينا .
She wasn't weak.
لم تكن ضعيفة.
I know she wasn't weak.
أعرف أنها لم تكن ضعيفة.
You're the one who's weak.
أنت الشخص الضعيف.
When you failed to join a key high school,
عندما فشلت في الانضمام إلى مدرسة ثانوية رئيسية،
your mom paid the school placement fee.
لقد دفعت والدتك رسوم الالتحاق بالمدرسة.
To pay that fee,
لدفع تلك الرسوم،
she refused to spend a cent on Ye Sibei.
رفضت أن تنفق سنتًا واحدًا على Ye Sibei.
Your sister found a way to finish high school
لقد وجدت أختك طريقة لإنهاء المدرسة الثانوية
and get into college.
والدخول إلى الكلية.
In college,
في الكلية،
you asked for money to date
لقد طلبت المال للمواعدة
and join clubs.
والانضمام إلى النوادي.
And your sister?
واختك؟
She worked part-time to make money.
عملت بدوام جزئي لكسب المال.
She even felt ashamed to ask your mom
حتى أنها شعرت بالخجل من أن تسأل أمك
for a computer.
لجهاز كمبيوتر.
After graduation,
بعد التخرج،
you ate what your family cook, used what they gave,
لقد أكلت ما طبخته عائلتك، واستخدمت ما قدموه لك،
lived under their roof and lived off them.
عاشوا تحت سقفهم وعاشوا منهم.
Even after marriage, you asked them for money.
حتى بعد الزواج طلبت منهم المال.
Ye Nianwen.
يي نيانوين.
Do you know where your down payment came from?
هل تعلم من أين جاءت دفعتك الأولى؟
It was your sister.
لقد كانت أختك.
She took a credit loan to help you.
لقد أخذت قرضًا ائتمانيًا لمساعدتك.
She borrowed 100,000 yuan.
لقد اقترضت 100 ألف يوان.
Ye Nianwen, don't you realize it?
يي نيان وين، ألا تدرك ذلك؟
Don't you know?
ألا تعلم؟
Nan.
في.
But I... I really didn't know about it.
ولكنني... لم أكن أعلم بذلك حقًا.
You're not supposed to know?
ليس من المفترض أن تعرف؟
Are you not supposed to know?
هل من المفترض أن لا تعرف؟
No.
لا.
You could have known.
كان بإمكانك أن تعرف.
You just didn't want to.
أنت فقط لم ترغب في ذلك.
Every time your parents did something wrong for you,
في كل مرة يفعل والدك شيئًا خاطئًا معك،
you chose to stay silent.
لقد اخترت البقاء صامتًا.
Because you enjoyed
لأنك استمتعت
everything taken from your sister.
كل شيء مأخوذ من أختك.
You were afraid to lose this easy life.
لقد كنت خائفًا من فقدان هذه الحياة السهلة.
Everything your sister
كل شيء أختك
sacrificed for you,
ضحى من أجلك
you always learned one step too late.
لقد تعلمت دائمًا خطوة واحدة متأخرًا.
And you'd apologize
وكنت تعتذر
to ease a bit of your guilt.
لتخفيف القليل من شعورك بالذنب.
Ye Nianwen.
يي نيانوين.
If you had lived like a man just once,
لو عشت كرجل ولو مرة واحدة،
your sister wouldn't be where she is today!
لن تكون أختك حيث هي اليوم!
You didn't dare report to the police.
لم تجرؤ على الإبلاغ للشرطة.
You keep saying it's for her good.
أنت تستمر في قول أن هذا من أجل مصلحتها.
Is that really for her good?
هل هذا حقا لصالحها؟
Do you not know how she lives now?
هل لا تعرف كيف تعيش الآن؟
You call that helping her?
هل تسمي ذلك مساعدتها؟
You just don't want trouble for yourselves.
أنتم فقط لا تريدون المتاعب لأنفسكم.
That way, everyone
بهذه الطريقة، الجميع
can keep living peacefully.
أستطيع أن أستمر في العيش بسلام.
Everyone but your sister.
الجميع ما عدا أختك.
But I truly hoped she...
ولكنني كنت آمل حقًا أنها...
You're just spineless.
أنت مجرد شخص ضعيف الشخصية.
You're a parasite.
أنت طفيلي.
You fed on your family's blood,
لقد تغذيت على دماء عائلتك،
yet pretend to be a just and kind hypocrite.
ومع ذلك يتظاهر بأنه منافق عادل ولطيف.
If you truly cared for her,
إذا كنت تهتم بها حقًا،
and loved your sister,
وأحببت أختك،
you'd have fought for her once.
لقد قاتلت من أجلها مرة واحدة.
You'd tell her
ستخبرها
she wasn't wrong.
لم تكن مخطئة.
She deserves to live
إنها تستحق أن تعيش
with her head held high.
مع رفع رأسها عاليا.
But have you ever done that?
ولكن هل فعلت ذلك من قبل؟
You haven't.
لم تفعل ذلك.
All these years,
كل هذه السنوات،
I kept wondering why Ye Sibei's life
لقد ظللت أتساءل لماذا حياة يي سيبي
turn out this way.
تتحول إلى هذا الشكل.
Now I finally understand.
الآن فهمت أخيرا.
It's because of your whole family.
هذا بسبب عائلتك بأكملها.
Every single one of you,
كل واحد منكم،
including me.
بما فيهم انا.
None of us ever told Ye Sibei
لم يخبر أحد منا يي سيبي أبدًا
she's never wrong for being born
إنها لم تخطئ أبدًا في ولادتها
and deserves to live well.
ويستحق أن يعيش جيدا.
Not once.
ولا مرة واحدة.
Maybe...
ربما...
Maybe even if I say it now,
ربما حتى لو قلت ذلك الآن،
you won't believe me.
لن تصدقني
But I really hope she'll always be
لكني آمل حقا أن تظل كذلك دائما
the Ye Sibei I admire most.
أنا معجب بـ Ye Sibei أكثر من أي شخص آخر.
Nan.
في.
I'll get going now.
سأذهب الآن.
Tonight is Dad's birthday.
اليوم هو عيد ميلاد أبي.
If you two aren't coming,
إذا لم تأتيا،
I'll tell Mom and Dad for you.
سأخبر أمي وأبي نيابة عنك.
Sorry, the number you dialed is powered off.
عذراً، الرقم الذي طلبته مغلق.
Sibei.
سيب.
Sibei!
سيب!
Qin Nan.
تشين نان.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
I'll take you to the hospital.
سأأخذك إلى المستشفى.
Sibei.
سيب.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
Sibei, wake up.
سيبي، استيقظ.
Talk to me.
تحدث معي.
Qin Nan.
تشين نان.
I wanted to fight, too.
أردت القتال أيضًا.
But I...
ولكن انا...
Every time I gathered courage,
في كل مرة أجمع فيها الشجاعة،
someone told me to endure.
لقد أخبرني أحدهم أن أتحمل.
They say it's for my good.
يقولون أنها لمصلحتي.
But
لكن
it's been so hard to endure.
لقد كان من الصعب جدًا تحمله.
Sibei.
سيب.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
You're not afraid of death,
أنت لا تخاف من الموت،
so why fear living?
فلماذا الخوف من الحياة؟
Qin Nan.
تشين نان.
I tried.
لقد حاولت.
I
أنا
really tried.
حاولت حقا.
I tried so hard to live.
لقد حاولت جاهدا أن أعيش.
(Ye Sibei)
(يي سيبي)
(Admission Letter)
(خطاب القبول)
(Welcome, New Students)
(مرحبا بالطلاب الجدد)
(Gaokao Countdown: 274 Days)
(العد التنازلي لاختبار غاوكاو: 274 يومًا)
Next, let's welcome
بعد ذلك، دعونا نرحب
Ye Sibei from Class 7, Year 1
يي سيبي من الصف السابع، السنة الأولى
to give her speech.
لإلقاء خطابها.
Please welcome her.
من فضلك رحب بها.
Come on, Sibei.
هيا يا سيبي.
(Nan City No. 2 High School)
(مدرسة نان سيتي الثانوية رقم 2)
Hello.
مرحبًا.
I'm Ye Sibei from Class 7, Year 1.
أنا يي سيبي من الصف السابع، السنة الأولى.
Today,
اليوم،
my speech topic is
موضوع خطابي هو
"The Best Is Always Yet to Come."
"الأفضل لم يأت بعد"
We strive.
نحن نسعى جاهدين.
We work hard.
نحن نعمل بجد.
We fight on.
نحن نواصل القتال.
We go through our darkest times.
نحن نمر بأوقاتنا المظلمة.
A bright future is within reach.
مستقبل مشرق في متناول اليد.
No hardship is insurmountable.
لا يوجد صعوبة لا يمكن التغلب عليها.
No despair lasts forever.
لا يأس يدوم إلى الأبد.
If your heart holds tomorrow,
إذا كان قلبك يحمل الغد،
then tomorrow will arrive just as you dream it.
ثم سيأتي الغد كما حلمت به.
On the road of growing up,
على طريق النمو،
we can chase dreams,
يمكننا مطاردة الأحلام،
create,
يخلق،
and grow wildly like spring.
وتنمو بشكل جامح مثل الربيع.
However,
لكن،
two great mountains stand before us.
جبلين عظيمين يقفان أمامنا.
One is denial.
الأول هو الإنكار.
The other, disdain.
والآخر، الازدراء.
They block our way forward.
إنهم يحجبون طريقنا للأمام.
They press down till we can't breathe.
إنهم يضغطون علينا حتى لا نتمكن من التنفس.
We give in.
نحن نستسلم.
We obey.
نحن نطيع.
We beg for mercy.
نحن نطلب الرحمة.
- My troublemaker! - The mountain...
-مُشَكِّلِي! -الجبل...
Where have you been?
أين كنت؟
What are you carrying there?
ماذا تحمل هناك؟
Put it down.
ضعها.
Gosh.
يا إلهي.
You just changed clothes.
لقد غيرت ملابسك للتو.
What's this?
ما هذا؟
It's all dirt and unwashed.
كلها أوساخ وغير مغسولة.
Take it off.
أخلعها.
It's fine, Mom.
لا بأس يا أمي.
I just took it out of the river.
لقد أخرجته للتو من النهر.
Why are you standing?
لماذا تقف؟
Close the door.
أغلق الباب.
Grab a cloth.
احضر قطعة قماش.
Don't move. Let me see if you hurt your hands.
لا تتحرك. دعني أرى إن كانت يديك تؤلمك.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
They're all red.
كلهم باللون الأحمر.
Quick.
سريع.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Take it off first.
أزلها أولاً.
Wait.
انتظر.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Wipe it clean.
امسحها نظيفة.
How heavy.
كم هو ثقيل.
You brat.
يا ولدي.
Let me see your hands.
دعني أرى يديك.
Rinse with water.
اشطفيه بالماء.
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Disinfect it with alcohol.
قم بتطهيره بالكحول.
Here.
هنا.
Disinfect it.
قم بتطهيره.
It'll sting. Bear with it.
سوف يؤلمك. تحمله.
Don't scream.
لا تصرخ.
Sibei.
سيب.
Come help me at the stall tomorrow.
تعال ساعدني في الموقف غدًا.
The stall?
الكشك؟
Mom.
أم.
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Sleep early tonight.
النوم مبكرا الليلة.
I'll wake you tomorrow.
سأوقظك غدا.
Breakfast rush is short.
فترة الإفطار قصيرة.
Customers leave if they see that I'm too busy.
الزبائن يغادرون إذا رأوا أنني مشغول للغاية.
Help me out,
ساعدني
and we'll earn more.
وسنكسب المزيد.
But I'm about to start Year 3.
ولكنني على وشك أن أبدأ السنة الثالثة.
Why should I work?
لماذا يجب علي أن أعمل؟
You want to study Year 3 and college, don't you?
تريد أن تدرس السنة الثالثة والجامعة، أليس كذلك؟
What about your brother?
ماذا عن أخيك؟
We just paid so much school placement fee for him.
لقد دفعنا للتو مبلغًا كبيرًا من رسوم التسجيل في المدرسة له.
How can we afford both of you?
كيف يمكننا أن نتحمل تكاليف كلاكما؟
I won't drop out.
لن انسحب.
I'll keep studying.
سأستمر في الدراسة.
Why are you so disobedient?
لماذا أنت عاصي هكذا؟
Don't you know
ألا تعلم؟
that your dad lost his job
أن والدك فقد وظيفته
because we had you.
لأننا كنا معك.
That's why life's so hard.
لهذا السبب الحياة صعبة للغاية.
You're lucky to study till now.
أنت محظوظ لأنك تدرس حتى الآن.
Why are you crying?
لماذا تبكي؟
Why can he study,
لماذا يستطيع الدراسة؟
but I can't?
ولكن لا استطيع؟
He's a boy.
إنه ولد.
He'll provide for his family and have a career.
سيوفر احتياجات أسرته وسيحصل على مهنة.
Without college,
بدون كلية،
how can he provide and succeed?
كيف يمكنه أن يوفر وينجح؟
What about me?
ماذا عني؟
What about my future?
ماذا عن مستقبلي؟
Sibei, you're a girl.
سيبي، أنت فتاة.
You'll marry one day.
سوف تتزوج يوما ما.
Besides, you're the eldest, right?
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، أنت الأكبر، أليس كذلك؟
The eldest should give in.
ينبغي على الأكبر أن يستسلم.
Your brother is the hope of the Ye family.
أخوك هو أمل عائلة يي.
He's our only way out.
إنه طريقنا الوحيد للخروج.
Mom.
أم.
I'll wake you in the morning.
سأوقظك في الصباح.
Almost there.
تقريبا هناك.
Keep it up.
استمر.
(Nanbei Breakfast)
(إفطار نانبي)
Sibei, why are you here?
سيبي، لماذا أنت هنا؟
Did you really drop out?
هل تركت الدراسة حقا؟
Well... Vegetable buns or meat buns?
حسنًا... كعكات الخضار أم كعكات اللحوم؟
How many?
كم عدد؟
Meat buns.
كعكات اللحم.
Two.
اثنين.
Two yuan.
اثنان يوان.
Sibei, you have such good grades.
سيبي، لديك درجات جيدة جدًا.
It's a pity you stopped studying.
من المؤسف أنك توقفت عن الدراسة.
Yeah.
نعم.
With your grades, college is certain.
مع درجاتك، الكلية مؤكدة.
Why did you quit school?
لماذا تركت المدرسة؟
Are you done?
هل انتهيت؟
Almost.
بالكاد.
- I've waited a long time. - Go to class first.
- لقد انتظرت لفترة طويلة. - اذهب إلى الفصل أولاً.
You'll be late.
سوف تتأخر.
- Bye. - Coming.
- وداعا. - قادم.
Two meat buns.
قطعتين من اللحم.
Drink it.
اشربه
Come on.
تعال.
Wait.
انتظر.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Be careful.
احرص.
Just a moment.
لحظة واحدة.
Sorry.
آسف.
One vegetable bun.
كعكة خضار واحدة.
Slow down.
ابطئ.
Mr. Yang.
السيد يانغ.
Sibei, quick, come sit.
سيبي، سريعًا، تعال واجلس.
Sibei.
سيب.
I have good news for you.
عندي لك أخبار جيدة.
You can go back to school.
يمكنك العودة إلى المدرسة.
Really?
حقًا؟
Really.
حقًا.
I can go back to school?
هل أستطيع العودة إلى المدرسة؟
Yes, you've received
نعم لقد استلمت
a targeted financial aid.
مساعدة مالية مستهدفة.
With this money,
مع هذه الأموال،
you can finish high school.
يمكنك إنهاء المدرسة الثانوية.
That's wonderful news.
هذه اخبار رائعة .
I always believed children should keep studying.
لقد اعتقدت دائمًا أن الأطفال يجب أن يستمروا في الدراسة.
But her mom thinks
لكن أمها تعتقد
girls don't need education.
الفتيات لا تحتاج إلى التعليم.
Now, that's solved.
الآن، تم حل هذا الأمر.
Sibei, come.
سيبي، تعال.
Thank Mr. Yang.
شكرا لك السيد يانغ.
Sit.
يجلس.
Mr. Yang.
السيد يانغ.
Who gave me the financial aid?
من أعطاني المساعدة المالية؟
Don't ask too many questions.
لا تسأل الكثير من الأسئلة.
The donor
المتبرع
doesn't want others to know
لا يريد أن يعرف الآخرون
too much about their identity.
الكثير عن هويتهم.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
this money wasn't easy to get.
لم يكن من السهل الحصول على هذه الأموال.
I just want to ask you.
أريد فقط أن أسألك.
Do you have the determination
هل لديك العزم
to keep studying hard?
لمواصلة الدراسة بجد؟
Yes.
نعم.
I do.
أفعل.
Mr. Yang, I want to study.
السيد يانغ أريد أن أدرس.
I want to go to college.
أريد أن أذهب إلى الكلية.
Good.
جيد.
Sibei, look.
سيبي، انظر.
this money is limited after all.
هذه الأموال محدودة بعد كل شيء.
After you finish high school,
بعد الانتهاء من المدرسة الثانوية،
you'll still need money for college.
لا يزال يتعين عليك الحصول على المال للدراسة الجامعية.
What's your plan then?
ما هي خطتك إذن؟
Mr. Yang.
السيد يانغ.
I checked.
لقد تأكدت.
College offers student loans,
تقدم الكلية قروضًا للطلاب،
and I can work part-time.
وأستطيع العمل بدوام جزئي.
All I need is a chance.
كل ما أحتاجه هو فرصة.
Good. That's what I hoped to hear.
حسنًا، هذا ما كنت أتمنى سماعه.
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
(I firmly believe)
(أنا أؤمن بشدة)
(we'll be like dandelions,)
(سنكون مثل الهندباء)
(Gaokao Countdown: 286 days) (breaking through the soil,)
(العد التنازلي لاختبار غاوكاو: 286 يومًا) (اختراق التربة)
(Gaokao Countdown: 274 days) (rising with the wind,)
(العد التنازلي لاختبار غاوكاو: 274 يومًا) (يرتفع مع الريح)
(Gaokao Countdown: 234 days) (and crossing mountains)
(العد التنازلي لـ Gaokao: 234 يومًا) (وعبور الجبال)
(to admire the view above)
(للإعجاب بالمنظر أعلاه)
(and the flowers in the mud below.)
(والزهور في الطين أدناه.)
(We're lonely,)
(نحن وحيدون)
(brave,)
(شجاع،)
(angry,)
(غاضب،)
(bright,)
(ساطع،)
(and never back down.)
(ولا تتراجع أبدًا.)
(I will never give up)
(لن أستسلم أبدًا)
(Gaokao Must-Do Practice Papers) (on becoming better.)
(أوراق عمل تدريبية ضرورية لامتحان Gaokao) (حول كيفية التحسن.)
(Gaokao Countdown: 0 days)
(العد التنازلي لاختبار Gaokao: 0 يوم)
(Welcome, New Students)
(مرحبا بالطلاب الجدد)
(Admission Letter)
(خطاب القبول)
I think I have a good chance this time.
أعتقد أن لدي فرصة جيدة هذه المرة.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Sounds good.
ًيبدو جيدا.
How did your day go?
كيف كان يومك؟
I interviewed with Hualing.
لقد أجريت مقابلة مع هوالينج.
- Not sure if I'll pass. - Sibei.
- لست متأكدًا من أنني سأمر. - سيبي.
- You're finally back.
- لقد عدت أخيرا.
Why didn't we see you at the job fair?
لماذا لم نراك في معرض العمل؟
I went to interview with Tengda Company.
ذهبت لإجراء مقابلة مع شركة Tengda.
Tengda?
متعلق ب؟
- So soon? - Tengda?
- بهذه السرعة؟ - ذات صلة؟
I heard Tengda is super strict with resume screening.
سمعت أن شركة Tengda صارمة للغاية في فحص السيرة الذاتية.
- Yeah. - Sibei, your resume is solid.
- نعم. - سيبي، سيرتك الذاتية جيدة.
They picked you right away.
لقد اختاروك على الفور.
Sibei. You forgot to remove the tag.
سيبي. نسيت إزالة العلامة.
Let me help.
دعني أساعدك.
No.
لا.
I still have to return it.
لا يزال يتعين علي إرجاعه.
I borrowed it just for the interview.
لقد استعرته فقط من أجل المقابلة.
- Smart move. - Sibei, you're always resourceful.
- خطوة ذكية. - سيبي، أنت دائمًا ما تكون ذكيًا.
I should've borrowed some too.
كان ينبغي لي أن استعير بعضًا منها أيضًا.
- I'll save some money. - Learn from her.
- سأوفر بعض المال. - تعلم منها.
- My wallet hurts. - Let's do it together later.
- محفظتي تؤلمني. - دعنا نفعل ذلك معًا لاحقًا.
Sure, we'll shop together next time.
بالتأكيد، سوف نتسوق معًا في المرة القادمة.
What makeup do you all use?
ما هو المكياج الذي تستخدمونه جميعا؟
Hello, Mom?
مرحبا أمي؟
Sibei.
سيب.
Have you considered coming back home?
هل فكرت بالعودة إلى المنزل؟
I found you a job at the local school
لقد وجدت لك وظيفة في المدرسة المحلية
that many people are eyeing.
أن العديد من الناس يتطلعون إلى ذلك.
Come back soon.
عد قريبا.
Stop finding me jobs.
توقف عن إيجاد وظائف لي.
I already have something here.
لدي شيء هنا بالفعل.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
You're not coming back?
أنت لن تعود؟
I'll talk to you later.
سأتحدث معك لاحقا.
Bye.
الوداع.
I just hope this afternoon's interview goes well.
أتمنى فقط أن تسير المقابلة بعد ظهر اليوم على ما يرام.
Smells good.
رائحته طيبة.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Your mom called again, asking you to go back home?
اتصلت بك والدتك مرة أخرى وتطلب منك العودة إلى المنزل؟
Yes.
نعم.
Your mom...
أمك...
You worked so hard to get into college.
لقد عملت بجد للالتحاق بالجامعة.
Why does she keep asking you to return?
لماذا تستمر في مطالبتك بالعودة؟
But it's easier to find a job back home.
ولكن من الأسهل العثور على عمل في وطنك.
And with her education, going back there
ومع تعليمها، والعودة إلى هناك
would be like a complete overkill.
سيكون مثل المبالغة الكاملة.
You're wrong.
أنت مخطئ.
It's not just about education background back home.
لا يتعلق الأمر فقط بالخلفية التعليمية في الوطن.
You also need the right connections.
تحتاج أيضًا إلى الاتصالات الصحيحة.
Our family isn't rich or influential.
عائلتنا ليست غنية أو مؤثرة.
I don't have the luxury to do nothing.
ليس لدي القدرة على عدم فعل أي شيء.
There are more chances in the city.
هناك فرص أكثر في المدينة.
At least it's fair.
على الأقل إنه عادل.
I'm staying.
انا باقية.
You've got a point.
لقد حصلت على نقطة.
But your mom...
ولكن أمك...
Can you win against her?
هل تستطيع الفوز عليها؟
I have to try whether I win.
يجب علي أن أحاول ما إذا كنت سأفوز.
Anyway, I'm set on not going back.
على أية حال، أنا مصمم على عدم العودة.
- That's not right. - Here's the meeting file.
- هذا ليس صحيحًا. - ها هو ملف الاجتماع.
Okay, thanks.
حسنًا، شكرًا لك.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
- Sibei, where's my coffee? - Thanks, Sibei.
- سيبي، أين قهوتي؟ - شكرا، سيبي.
Right here.
هنا.
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Don't mention it.
لا تذكرها.
Mr. Liu.
السيد ليو.
Your delivery.
تسليمك.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Ling.
آخر.
This one's yours.
هذه لك.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Ms. Wang, this is yours.
السيدة وانغ، هذا لك.
Ye Sibei.
أيها سيبي.
Meeting in ten minutes.
اجتماع بعد عشر دقائق.
Prepare the conference room.
إعداد قاعة المؤتمرات.
Okay.
تمام.
Who can help sort this morning's meeting agenda?
من يستطيع المساعدة في ترتيب جدول أعمال اجتماع هذا الصباح؟
I can.
أنا استطيع.
Everyone, Ms. Liu is sick.
الجميع، السيدة ليو مريضة.
Who can handle this quarter's financial report?
من يستطيع التعامل مع التقرير المالي لهذا الربع؟
I can.
أنا استطيع.
We're short-staffed in supplies.
نحن نعاني من نقص في الموظفين في الإمدادات.
Who can lend a hand?
من يستطيع تقديم المساعدة؟
I can.
أنا استطيع.
Sibei.
سيب.
You work hard.
أنت تعمل بجد.
Keep it up.
استمر.
If there's a permanent spot,
إذا كان هناك مكان دائم،
you'll be my first choice.
سوف تكون خياري الأول.
Thank you, Mr. Li.
شكرا لك السيد لي.
I'll continue working hard.
سأستمر في العمل الجاد.
(There is no happier thing in the world than to fight for an ideal)
(لا يوجد شيء أسعد في العالم من النضال من أجل المثل الأعلى)
(Pay Slip)
(إيصال الراتب)
(Nianwen: Sibei.)
(نيانوين: سيبي.)
(I want to buy a PSP.)
(أريد شراء PSP.)
(Can you)
(هل تستطيع)
(give me some money?)
(أعطني بعض المال؟)
(I'll transfer it to you later.)
(سأنقله إليك لاحقًا.)
Be careful not to drop it.
احذر من إسقاطه.
You're back.
لقد عدت.
Cooking?
طبخ؟
(Mom: You make just over 2,000 yuan a month,)
(الأم: أنت تكسب ما يزيد قليلاً عن 2000 يوان في الشهر)
(and you have to rent a place.)
(ويجب عليك استئجار مكان.)
(I don't know what you're working so hard for.)
(لا أعلم لماذا تعمل بجد من أجل ذلك.)
(Don't be so selfish.)
(لا تكن أنانيًا جدًا.)
(You ignore your whole family,)
(أنت تتجاهل عائلتك بأكملها)
(just to live your own carefree life.)
(فقط لتعيش حياتك الخالية من الهموم.)
(Tengda Construction Group)
(مجموعة البناء ذات الصلة)
Hello, Madam.
مرحبا سيدتي.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
I'm Ye Sibei's mother.
أنا والدة يي سيبي.
I'm here to see my daughter.
أنا هنا لرؤية ابنتي.
Madam.
سيدتي.
We don't allow anyone to enter.
نحن لا نسمح لأحد بالدخول.
Ye Sibei is in a meeting right now.
يي سيبي في اجتماع الآن.
Have a seat for a bit.
خذ مقعدا قليلا.
Wait here for a moment.
انتظر هنا لحظة.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Okay, let's take a look
حسنًا، دعونا نلقي نظرة
at an overview of this project first.
نظرة عامة على هذا المشروع أولاً.
First, the location.
أولاً الموقع.
It's in Linjiang City, Jiangbei New District.
يقع في مدينة Linjiang، منطقة Jiangbei الجديدة.
To the east is International Eco Conference Plaza.
إلى الشرق يوجد مركز المؤتمرات البيئي الدولي.
To the west, Guanshan Lake's mountains.
إلى الغرب، جبال بحيرة قوانشان.
And the design uses...
ويستخدم التصميم...
Sibei.
سيب.
Lunch is here. Go grab it.
الغداء هنا، اذهب واحصل عليه.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's continue.
دعونا نستمر.
Hello, your order's here.
مرحبًا، طلبك هنا.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
So this is the job you found in the city?
إذن هذه هي الوظيفة التي وجدتها في المدينة؟
Serving tea and running errands.
تقديم الشاي وتنفيذ المهمات.
Waiting on other people.
انتظار الآخرين.
Mom, what are you doing here?
أمي ماذا تفعلين هنا؟
I came to see you.
لقد جئت لرؤيتك.
You don't miss us, but we miss you.
أنت لا تفتقدنا، لكننا نفتقدك.
I just don't get it.
انا لا أفهم ذلك.
What's so great about the city?
ما هو الشيء العظيم في المدينة؟
Why won't you come home?
لماذا لا تعود إلى المنزل؟
You don't answer calls or reply to messages.
لا تجيب على المكالمات أو الرسائل.
- Mom. - Let me take a good look.
- أمي. - دعيني ألقي نظرة جيدة.
Mom, what are you doing?
أمي ماذا تفعلين؟
Part of the construction development...
جزء من تطوير البناء...
Come on, let's eat.
هيا لنأكل.
I didn't even wear gloves.
ولم أرتدي حتى القفازات.
Come on, time to eat.
هيا، حان وقت الأكل.
What a big company.
ماهذه الشركة الكبيرة؟
There are so many people here, yet no one helps my girl.
هناك الكثير من الناس هنا، ولكن لا أحد يساعد ابنتي.
Aren't you just bullying
هل أنت مجرد تنمر؟
a kid fresh out of college?
طفل حديث التخرج من الكلية؟
Here, take this.
هنا، خذ هذا.
Let me feed you.
دعني اطعمك.
I'm telling you. She quits!
أنا أقول لك، إنها تستقيل!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
What did you do?
ماذا فعلت؟
What?
ماذا؟
Don't make a scene, alright?
لا تصنع مشهدًا، حسنًا؟
I'm about to become permanent.
أنا على وشك أن أصبح دائمًا.
I'm taking you home.
سأأخذك إلى المنزل.
Turning permanent?
التحول الدائم؟
You're still dreaming.
مازلت تحلم
I'm telling you.
انا أخبرك.
I'm staying right here today. I'll wait all day.
سأبقى هنا اليوم. سأنتظر طوال اليوم.
Wherever you go, I follow.
أينما ذهبت، أتبعك.
You're doing this on purpose?
هل تفعل هذا عمدا؟
If you want to bring me back to Nancheng...
إذا كنت تريد إعادتي إلى نانشينغ...
I'm telling you.
انا أخبرك.
I won't agree.
لن أوافق.
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Who's the boss here?
من هو الرئيس هنا؟
Boss, let me tell you something.
يا رئيس، اسمح لي أن أخبرك بشيء.
I'm Ye Sibei's mother.
أنا والدة يي سيبي.
I hereby announce my daughter's quitting.
أعلن هنا عن استقالة ابنتي.
Why's that?
لماذا هذا؟
This company is terrible.
هذه الشركة فظيعة.
- Mom! - All dressed up, yet...
- أمي! - كل شيء يرتدي ملابسه، ولكن...
You can't even say thanks after getting tea served to you.
لا يمكنك حتى أن تقول شكرًا بعد تقديم الشاي لك.
What's wrong with this woman?
ماذا حدث لهذه المرأة؟
Madam, who are you calling terrible?
سيدتي من الذي تسمينه فظيعًا؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I didn't expect her mom to...
لم أتوقع أن أمها ستفعل...
I'm sorry, boss.
انا آسف يا رئيس.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I...
أنا آسف. أنا آسف. أنا...
Enough, stop talking.
كفى، توقف عن الكلام.
I've seen enough.
لقد رأيت ما يكفي.
Ye.
نعم.
Why did you bring your family drama to work?
لماذا جلبت الدراما العائلية إلى العمل؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
From today on,
من اليوم فصاعدا،
you're fired.
لقد تم طردك.
Leave the company.
أترك الشركة
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Sir, please give me another chance.
سيدي، من فضلك أعطني فرصة أخرى.
Enough, stop talking.
كفى، توقف عن الكلام.
Go to HR for your resignation.
اذهب إلى قسم الموارد البشرية للحصول على استقالتك.
She got fired.
لقد تم طردها.
She just graduated. Finding a job isn't easy.
لقد تخرّجت للتو. إيجاد وظيفة ليس بالأمر السهل.
She was about to get permanent.
لقد كانت على وشك أن تصبح دائمة.
Ms. Wang.
السيدة وانغ.
Ms. Wang, what are you doing? Ms. Wang.
آنسة وانغ، ماذا تفعلين؟ آنسة وانغ.
Young lady.
سيدة شابة.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I've spoken to you several times.
لقد تحدثت معك عدة مرات.
If you don't pay rent,
إذا لم تدفع الإيجار،
I have no choice but to make you leave this way,
ليس لدي خيار سوى أن أجعلك تغادر بهذه الطريقة،
Didn't I tell you?
ألم أخبرك؟
I've already paid the agency.
لقد دفعت للوكالة بالفعل.
I've been calling them every day.
لقد كنت أتصل بهم كل يوم.
Young lady, don't you get it?
أيتها الشابة، ألا تفهمين ذلك؟
The agency took your money and ran.
الوكالة أخذت أموالك وهربت.
Aren't you silly?
أليس أنت سخيف؟
I'm also contacting Consumer Association, Ms. Wang.
أنا أيضًا أتواصل مع جمعية المستهلكين، السيدة وانج.
Young lady.
سيدة شابة.
Get your head straight.
اجعل رأسك مستقيما.
This kind of thing won't have any result.
هذا النوع من الأشياء لن يكون له أي نتيجة.
I can't wait for you either.
أنا أيضا لا أستطيع الانتظار لك.
I need the money.
أحتاج إلى المال.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Ms. Wang.
السيدة وانغ.
Give me a few more days.
أعطني بضعة أيام أخرى.
Okay?
تمام؟
Ms. Wang, give me a few more days.
السيدة وانج، أعطيني بضعة أيام أخرى.
I'm trying to raise the money, Ms. Wang.
أحاول جمع المال، سيدتي وانج.
(Mingdu Hotel)
(فندق مينغدو)
(Discounted Single Room 40 Yuan Per Day)
(غرفة فردية مخفضة 40 يوانًا في اليوم)
(This Internet Café, 15 Yuan For Overnight Stay)
(هذا مقهى الإنترنت ؟؟، 15 يوان للإقامة لليلة واحدة)
♪The words they said♪
???الكلمات التي قالوها؟؟؟
♪I have never forgotten♪
???لم أنسى أبدا؟؟؟
Overnight time's up.
لقد انتهى وقت الليل.
If you want to keep playing,
إذا كنت تريد الاستمرار في اللعب،
go to the front desk to renew.
اذهب إلى مكتب الاستقبال لتجديد.
♪Endured so many cold stares♪
???تحملت كل هذه النظرات الباردة؟؟؟
♪Taken so many hits♪
???تلقيت الكثير من الضربات؟؟؟
♪Just to become unstoppable♪
???فقط لكي تصبح لا يمكن إيقافك؟؟؟
♪Stopping♪
؟؟؟وقف؟؟؟
♪Stopping them only makes me stronger♪
???إيقافهم يجعلني أقوى؟
♪Smash through the walls of reality♪
???تحطيم جدران الواقع؟؟؟
♪Carry my bag and explore♪
???حمل حقيبتي واستكشف؟؟؟
♪Step by step, always on the road♪
???خطوة بخطوة، دائمًا على الطريق???
♪So I won't feel panic♪
???لذلك لن أشعر بالذعر؟؟؟
♪I was born stubborn♪
???لقد ولدت عنيدة؟؟؟
♪A blazing sun♪
???شمس حارقة؟؟؟
♪I insist on going against the wind♪
???أصر على الذهاب ضد الريح؟؟؟
♪Soaring with all my might♪
???أرتفع بكل قوتي؟؟؟
♪If darkness dares to stop me♪
???إذا تجرأ الظلام على إيقافي؟؟؟
♪I'll be the light that tears through the night♪
"سأكون الضوء الذي يمزق الليل"
♪I'm on the stage that belongs to me♪
???أنا على المسرح الذي يخصني؟؟؟
♪Fearless♪
???لا يعرف الخوف???
♪Blooming♪
???مزهرة؟؟؟
♪I was born stubborn♪
???لقد ولدت عنيدة؟؟؟
♪A blazing sun♪
???شمس حارقة؟؟؟
(Resume, Ye Sibei)
(استئناف، يي سيبي)
♪Soaring with all my might♪
???أرتفع بكل قوتي؟؟؟
♪If darkness dares to stop me♪
???إذا تجرأ الظلام على إيقافي؟؟؟
♪I'll be the light that tears through the night♪
"سأكون الضوء الذي يمزق الليل"
♪I'm on the stage that belongs to me♪
???أنا على المسرح الذي يخصني؟؟؟
♪Fearless♪
???لا يعرف الخوف???
♪Blooming♪
???مزهرة؟؟؟
♪Why is there always someone trying to make me surrender?♪
لماذا هناك دائما شخص يحاول أن يجعلني أستسلم ؟؟؟؟
♪There's a gray cloud in your eyes♪
???هل هناك سحابة رمادية في عينيك؟؟؟
♪But I see a long letter through the clouds♪
???ولكنني أرى رسالة طويلة من خلال السحب؟؟؟
♪You hide your emotions, staying silent♪
???أنت تخفي مشاعرك وتظل صامتًا؟؟؟
♪I wish I could accompany you back to the clear sky♪
???أتمنى أن أتمكن من مرافقتك إلى السماء الصافية؟؟؟
♪If I could capture your shadow♪
????إذا كان بإمكاني التقاط ظلك؟؟؟
♪I wouldn't mind wandering again♪
???لن أمانع في التجول مرة أخرى؟؟؟
♪Moreover, my light is in your life♪
???علاوة على ذلك، نوري موجود في حياتك؟؟؟
♪So I must trust in myself♪
???لذا يجب أن أثق بنفسي؟؟؟
♪Please let me become you♪
???من فضلك اسمح لي أن أصبحك؟؟؟
♪The secret that you can tell♪
???السر الذي يمكنك أن تقوله؟؟؟
♪Becoming the gentle fragrance that heals your past♪
???تصبح العطر اللطيف الذي يشفي ماضيك؟؟؟
♪If fate insists on drenching you♪
???إذا أصر القدر على إغراقك؟؟؟
♪With a torrential downpour♪
???مع هطول أمطار غزيرة؟؟؟
♪Don't be afraid, I am your soul's coat♪
???لا تخف، أنا معطف روحك؟؟؟
♪Please let me become you♪
???من فضلك اسمح لي أن أصبحك؟؟؟
♪Believing in the proof of love♪
???الإيمان بدليل الحب؟؟؟
♪Becoming the island where every dream of yours rests♪
???هل ستصبح الجزيرة التي يستقر فيها كل حلم لديك؟???
♪Don't lament the lost scenery♪
???لا تندب المشهد المفقود؟؟؟
♪As time passes♪
???مع مرور الوقت؟؟؟
♪I will still be here♪
???سوف أظل هنا؟؟؟
♪Not forgetting to accompany you to the edges of the rest of life♪
???لا ننسى أن نرافقك إلى حواف بقية الحياة؟؟؟